Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4212
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Garment Workers of America AFL, 1945-1955 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  November 13 1945 - April 25 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Guard Union of America, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  January 21 1952 - April 15 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Guards' and Watchmen's Union, 1953-1955 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  May 8 1953 - March 4 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers AFL, 1946-1961 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  May 28 1946 - May 2 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers Union of America AFL, 1947-1959 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  July 16 1947 - October 6 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Hollywood Film Council, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  May 20 1958 - October 12 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union of Journeymen of the Horseshoers of the U.S. and Canada, 1951-1956 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  June 18 1951 - March 5 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1945-1961 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  November 28 1945 - June 8 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954-1961 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  March 12 1954 - December 8 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1947-1952 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  March 10 1947 - July 15 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Idaho State AFL-CIO, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  July 21 1959 - March 24 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Idaho State Federation of Labor, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  January 18 1950 - March 1 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. Illinois State Industrial Union Council, 1948-1958 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  May 27 1948 - March 27 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Illinois State Federation of Labor, 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  January 18 1950 - October 19 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Illinois, 1949-1960 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  March 17 1949 - October 3 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Independent Union Council, 1954-1960 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  February 8 1954 - September 29 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Alliance of Independent Unions, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  May 20 1958 - October 17 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Allied Independent Unions, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  January 16 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Indiana State Federation of Labor, 1950-1961 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  January 18 1950 - June 14 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Indiana State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1956 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  February 17 1950 - July 6 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Industrial Trades Union of America, 1946-1952 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  May 29 1946 - January 16 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Industrial Workers of the World, 1951-1957 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  September 20 1951 - October 10 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union of Allied Industrial Workers of America, 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  October 29 1956 - January 1 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union of Life Insurance Agents, 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  December 14 1949 - January 24 1961
- Union Correspondence. Insurance Agents International Union, 1953-1959 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  February 24 1953 - January 30 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Insurance and Allied Workers Organizing Committee, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  October 10 1951 - October 12 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Insurance Workers of America, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  August 24 1959 - July 5 1960
- Union Correspondence. International Labor Press of America, 1953-1958 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  December 11 1953 - May 7 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Iowa, 1955-1960 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  April 7 1955 - April 20 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Iowa State Federation of Labor, 1950-1952 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  January 18 1950 - April 17 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Iowa State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1955 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  February 17 1950 - October 7 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1945-1961 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  November 6 1945 - October 13 1961
- Union Correspondence. Jersey Standard Tanker Officers Association, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  February 6 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Jewelry Workers' Union, 1949-1960 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  December 14 1949 - March 9 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Jewish Labor Committee, 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  November 4 1953 - March 2 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Kansas State Federation of Labor, 1950-1957 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  January 18 1950 - July 11 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Kansas State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1952 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  February 17 1950 - January 6 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Kentucky State Federation of Labor, 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  November 19 1953 - October 1 1956
- Union Correspondence. Kentucky, 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  June 25 1958 - April 26 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Kentucky State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1954 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  February 19 1950 - March 9 1954
- Union Correspondence. Labor Policy Association, Inc., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  December 8 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Amalgamated Lace Operatives of America, 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  December 14 1949 - November 15 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union of Wood, Wire and Metal Lathers, 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  October 14 1949 - October 19 1961
- Union Correspondence. Laundry and Dry Cleaning International Union, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  July 22 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Laundry Workers International Union AFL, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  May 25 1949 - February 5 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers Union, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  September 11 1959 - September 9 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Leather Workers International Union, 1949-1960 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  December 14 1949 - October 4 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Association of Letter Carriers AFL, 1949-1955 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  December 14 1949 - March 15 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Rural Letter Carriers' Association, 1949-1957 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  December 14 1949 - February 20 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Amalgamated Lithographers of America, 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  October 21 1949 - October 18 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1945-1962 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  November 9 1945 - January 25 1962
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Brotherhood of Longshoremen, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  June 22 1956 - January 13 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Longshoremen's Association AFL, 1954-1960 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  August 23 1954 - January 27 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union CIO, 1947-1961 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  April 24 1947 - May 8 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Louisiana State Federation of Labor, 1950-1952 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  January 19 1950 - February 7 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Louisiana State Industrial Union Council, 1949-1952 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  May 18 1949 - August 20 1952
- 1949-1952 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Labor Union Correspondence. Machine Printers Beneficial Association (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Association of Machinists, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  March 11 1959 - May 25 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Association of Machinists, 1953-1958 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  February 9 1953 - December 2 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Association of Machinists, 1945-1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  December 10 1945 - March 16 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Mailers Union, 1949-1960 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  December 15 1949 - September 30 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Maine State Federation of Labor, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  May 14 1953 - October 15 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. Maine State Industrial Union, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  February 13 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees AFL, 1946-1960 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  January 4 1946 - December 6 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Association of Marble, Slate and Stone Polishers, Rubbers and Sawyers, Tile and Marble Setters Helpers and Terrazzo Helpers, 1949-1961 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  December 23 1949 - April 24 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards CIO, 1948-1952 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  May 7 1948 - February 12 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Maine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1948-1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  November 29 1948 - April 7 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Marine Engineers, 1957-1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  January 18 1957 - November 10 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Pacific Coast Marine Firemen, Oilers, Watertenders and Wipers Association, 1949-1956 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  December 23 1949 - June 25 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  November 28 1945 - July 12 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Maryland Industrial Union Council, CIO, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  September 18 1951 - July 16 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. Maryland State: District of Columbia Federation of Labor, 1950-1961 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  January 19 1950 - December 12 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Massachusetts State Federation of Labor, 1948-1951 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  December 10 1948 - March 19 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Massachusetts State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  February 13 1950 - February 13 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Maritime Union of America, 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  November 27 1945 - March 16 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots of America, 1949-1958 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  December 23 1949 - September 30 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America AFL, 1947-1960 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  March 13 1947 - July 15 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. General Society of Mechanics and Tradesmen, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  June 25 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Mechanics Educational Society of America, 1948-1953 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  January 19 1948 - November 4 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. The National Association of Special Delivery Messengers, 1949-1958 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  December 23 1949 - May 5 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Metal Engravers and Marking Device Workers Union, 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  May 14 1953 - March 5 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers and Helpers International Union, 1945-1958 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  November 27 1945 - February 4 1958
- Union Correspondence. Michigan, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  August 15 - October 31 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Michigan CIO Council, 1949-1956 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  November 7 1949 - August 8 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Michigan State Federation of Labor, 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  September 27 1949 - July 27 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers CIO, 1948-1961 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  January 14 1948 - March 21 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Progressive Mine Workers of America, 1949-1952 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  December 23 1949 - February 18 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Minnesota AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  October 29 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Minnesota State Federation of Labor, 1949-1958 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  October 14 1949 - March 27 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Minnesota State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1956 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  February 13 1950 - March 10 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Mississippi State Federation of Labor, 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  January 19 1950 - January 14 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. Missouri State Federation of Labor, 1949-1961 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  September 27 1949 - October 24 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Missouri State Industrial Union Council, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  February 16 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Molders and Foundry Workers Union of North America AFL, 1945-1958 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  November 20 1945 - March 24 1958
- Union Correspondence. Montana State AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  August 14 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Montana State federation of Labor, 1951-1957 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  March 20 1951 - July 11 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Montana State Industrial Union Council, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Musicians, 1948-1962 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  March 5 1948 - January 19 1962
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- General Correspondence. National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1955-1961 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  March 23 1955 - July 25 1961
- General Correspondence. National Labor Service, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  December 3 and 20 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Sharecroppers Fund, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  April 14 1958 - October 26 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Union of Mine Workers, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  September 1 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. Nebraska State Federation of Labor, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  January 23 1950 - November 12 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Nebraska State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  February 16 1950 - March 10 1952
- Union Correspondence. Negro American Labor Council, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  July 8 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Nevada State Federation of Labor, 1950-1961 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  January 23 1950 - November 15 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. New Hampshire State Federation of Labor, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  January 23 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. New Hampshire State Industrial Union Council, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Labor Union Correspondence. New Jersey, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  February 25 1949 - October 27 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. New Jersey State CIO Council, 1949-1957 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  April 11 1949 - February 21 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. New Jersey State Federation of Labor, 1949-1955 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  April 11 1949 - April 7 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. New Mexico State Federation of Labor, 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  January 23 1950 - November 4 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. New York, 1947-1959 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  December 17 1947 - July 30 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. New York City, 1948-1961 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  March 16 1948 - January 18 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. New York State AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  February 5 1960 - October 20 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. New York State CIO Council, 1945-1960 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  November 30 1945 - March 22 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. New York State Federation of Labor, 1945-1954 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  November 30 1945 - August 5 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Newspaper Guild CIO, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  February 9 1959 - January 31 1962
- Labor Union Correspondence. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York and Vicinity, 1949-1958 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  March 22 1949 - April 9 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. North Carolina State Federation of Labor, 1950-1960 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  January 24 1950 - April 25 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. North Dakota State Federation of Labor, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  February 24 1950 - January 8 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Office Employees' International Union AFL, 1947-1960 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  March 11 1947 - September 22 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Ohio, 1952-1959 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  April 9 1952 - July 14 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Ohio State Federation of Labor, 1950-1961 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  January 24 1950 - August 1 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Ohio State Industrial Union Council, 1949-1956 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  September 29 1949 - October 1 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1955-1961 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  March 14 1955 - July 26 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Oklahoma State Federation of Labor, 1950-1956 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  January 24 1950 - November 2 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Oklahoma State Industrial Union Council, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  February 16 and April 28 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Optical Workers Conference, 1954-1958 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  July 9 1954 - January 16 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Oregon State Federation of Labor, 1949-1955 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  September 27 1949 - November 9 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Brotherhood of Packinghouse Workers, 1949-1960 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  December 23 1949 - June 8 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Packinghouse Workers of America CIO, 1946-1961 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  December 20 1946 - March 8 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America AFL, 1947-1960 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  July 30 1947 - November 12 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Pennsylvania, 1948-1958 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  June 18 1948 - July 18 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  March 24 1958 - February 18 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Pattern Makers' League of North America AFL, 1945-1952 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  November 16 1945 - October 9 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Paving Cutters' Union of the United States and Canada, 1951-1955 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  February 24 1951 - May 21 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. Pennsylvania State Federation of Labor, 1948-1961 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  June 10 1948 - June 6 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Pennsylvania CIO Council, 1950-1958 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  February 16 1950 - August 15 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Operative Plasterers' and Cement Finishers International Association of the US and Canada AFL, 1946-1961 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  July 25 1946 - September 12 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Plate Printers, Die Stampers and Engravers' Union of North America AFL, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  September 27 1949 - February 3 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. Playthings, Jewelry and Novelty Workers International Union CIO, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  September 21 and November 17 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Federation of Post Office Clerks AFL, 1948-1960 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  September 3 1948 - November 2 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. United National Association of Post Office Clerks, 1950-1958 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  November 9 1950 - March 14 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. United National Association of Post Office Craftsmen, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  October 22 1958 - May 18 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Post Office and General Service Employees, 1952-1958 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  October 9 1952 - February 25 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Federation of Post Office Motor Vehicle Employees, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  April 30 1958 - August 31 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Alliance of Postal Employees, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  January 23 1952 - September 22 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. The National Association of Postal Supervisors AFL, 1950-1961 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  September 21 1950 - December 20 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Postal Transport Association, 1955-1960 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  December 14 1955 - January 26 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. National League of District Postmasters of the US, 1951-1960 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  December 4 1951 - October 3 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Brotherhood of Operative Potters, 1950-1959 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  March 2 1950 - July 16 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America AFL, 1948-1956 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  February 13 1948 - March 20 1956
- Union Correspondence. National Council of Professional Employees, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  April 4 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Puerto Rico Free Federation of Labor AFL, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  February 2 1950 - March 30 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1948-1961 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  September 3 1948 - July 25 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Radio and Television Directors Guild, 1955-1959 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  May 23 1955 - September 29 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Railroad Employees, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  June 26 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Railroad Operating Crafts, 1954-1956 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  August 2 1954 - August 12 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Railroad Shop crafts of America, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  February 9 1949
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America AFL, 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  November 28 1945 - May 26 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Order of Railroad Telegraphers AFL, 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  December 7 1945 - April 26 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  December 5 1945 - April 20 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Railroad Yardmasters of America AFL, 1946-1961 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  July 25 1946 - April 20 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Railroad Yardmasters of North America, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  February 24 1949 - September 27 1949
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  December 11 1945 - June 29 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America AFL, 1946-1961 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  July 25 1946 - September 18 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Order of Railway Conductors of America, 1945-1959 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  December 7 1945 - October 27 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Railway Mail Association AFL, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  March 3 1949
- Labor Union Correspondence. Railway Supervisors Association, Inc., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  March 1 1949
- Labor Union Correspondence. Association of Colored Railway Trainmen and Locomotive Firemen, 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  March 3 1949 - January 6 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Retail Clerks International Association AFL, 1945-1962 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  December 4 1945 - January 19 1962
- Labor Union Correspondence. Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union CIO, 1953-1961 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  February 9 1953 - October 20 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Rhode Island State Federation of Labor, 1950-1957 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  February 2 1950 - October 11 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Rhode Island State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  February 16 1950 - January 30 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Slate Tile and Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers Association, 1950-1954 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  November 1 1950 - December 1 1954
- United Rubber, Cork Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1946-1962 (Box 6, Folder 123)
- Labor Union Correspondence. Lake Sailors Union, 1956-1961 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  November 26 1956 - February 7 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Federation of Salaried Unions, 1950-1955 (Box 6, Folder 125)